# **NGUYEN ANH CHUNG**

### .NET Developer

Vinh, Nghe An | 0975453374 | <u>anhchungitsme@gmail.com</u> | <u>github.com/chicharitoachs</u>



## Summary

I learn new stuff every day to be on a top of .NET technologies and best practices. I have been working with .NET more than 3 years.

Learning new languages and technologies is what I am passionate about. I'm trying to follow in my project code style, best practices, use documentation and best experience of OOP programming: MVC, design patterns and etc..

By the way, I interesting in time-management and management overall.

Most my free time, I'm trying to release my ideas in real life.

I'm loving to be a team member. It's a great opportunity to share your experience and meet a great people.

And I'm trying to become a full stack developer and technical leader.

### **Technical Skills**

### • Programming Languages:

- Vb.NET, C#.NET
- Javascript
- HTML, CSS

#### • Frameworks/Platforms:

- AngularJS
- ASP.NET MVC, Entity Framework, LinQ to SQL
- ASP Web API, RestfulAPI, Json/XML
- ¡Query, Bootstrap, Semantic UI
- DevExpress Winform
- Kendo UI

#### Database Management Systems:

- MS SQL Server
- MySQL

#### Version Control:

- SVN (TortoiseSVN & VisualSVN)

#### Soft Skills:

- Time management
- Teamwork
- Business communication

#### IDE:

- Visual Studio

#### Other:

- Good understanding about the SCRUM process
- Understanding about OOP, Design Pattern, Dependency Injection
- Understanding software design, database design
- Hardworking, mature and a good team player
- Good time management, teamwork skill..

### **Work History**

➤ 04/2018 – 04/2019: Dong Kinh Copmany | website: <u>dkc.com.vn</u>

**1. Archives** 04/2018 – 04/2019

#### • Description:

- Technologies: Web Asp.NET- MVC 5 (Back-end), AngularJS (Front-end)
- Languages: C#.NET, Html/Css, jQuery
- As the need for record-keeping increased, integrity and preservation that need to be addressed. Storage system writing was developed.
- Team Size: 8
- Responsibilities:
  - Code full-stack functionalities for products
  - Develop and fix the application's defect base on requirements
  - Write key technical documents and mentor new members of the team
- ➤ 11/2015 03/2018: I'm a member of product team in VTN Software | website: vtnsoft.com
  - 1. **VTN Software** 11/2015 01/2017
  - Project: VTN HIS, VTN Clinic, VTN LIS
  - Description:
    - Technologies: Winforms used Control DevExpress

- Languages: Vb.Net
- Management of patient registration informations on a Hospital or Clinic
- Design UX/UI and implement the solution (both back-end and front-end) based on the requirements from stakeholders
- Team Size: 8Responsibilities:
  - Develop and fix the application's defect base on requirements
  - Develop small modules of the system

#### 2. **VTN Software** 02/2017 – 06/2017

Project: Register Online System (of VTN HIS)

- Description:
  - Technologies: Web Asp.NET, MVC 5
  - Languages: C#.NET, Html/Css, jQuery
  - A system the process of registration and patient. A system connecting to VTN HIS Software. The purpose of the system is to help to transfer registration informations to VTN HIS Software
- Team Size: 3
- Responsibilities:
  - Design database schema and implement back-end services for the web application
  - Code full-stack functionalities for products
  - Develop and fix the application's defect base on requirements
  - Collaborate with team leader to develop procedures for products
  - Write key technical documents and mentor new members of the team

3. **VTN Software** 07/2017 – 03/2018

- Project: Human Resource Management (VTN HRM)
- Description:
  - Technologies: Web Asp.Net Core 2.0 MVC 5
  - Languages: C#.NET, Html/Css, jQuery
  - The purpose of the system is to help to manage employees on Hospital or Clinic
  - Team Size: 3
- Responsibilities:
  - Design database schema and implement back-end services for the web application
  - Code full-stack functionalities for products
  - Develop and fix the application's defect base on requirements
  - Collaborate with team leader to develop procedures for products
  - Write key technical documents and mentor new members of the team

## **Education**

> Engineer 2011 - 2015

Vinh University of Technology Education Graduate software engineering 2015